[
  {
    "question": "オラスポア",
    "correct": "セフロキサジン",
    "choices": [
      "セフロキサジン",
      "ジサイクロミン・アルミニウム",
      "アナストロゾール",
      "カンデサルタンシレキセチル・ヒドロクロロチアジド"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "リウマトレックス",
    "correct": "メトトレキサート",
    "choices": [
      "メトトレキサート",
      "フラボキサート",
      "セフカペンピボキシル",
      "ケトコナゾール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ゾフルーザ",
    "correct": "バロキサビルマルボキシル",
    "choices": [
      "セフカペンピボキシル",
      "バロキサビルマルボキシル",
      "ピタバスタチンカルシウム",
      "フルニトラゼパム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "エリキュース",
    "correct": "アピキサバン",
    "choices": [
      "ジフルコルトロンエステル・リドカイン",
      "ジアゼパム",
      "レボフロキサシン",
      "アピキサバン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アメナリーフ",
    "correct": "アメナメビル",
    "choices": [
      "ナルフラフィン",
      "ベプリジル",
      "マプロチリン",
      "アメナメビル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "イーケプラ",
    "correct": "レベチラセタム",
    "choices": [
      "フルチカゾンフランカルボンエステル",
      "オウヒエキス",
      "ニトラゼパム",
      "レベチラセタム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "カナリア",
    "correct": "テネリグリプチンカナグリフロジン",
    "choices": [
      "フェルビナク",
      "ミコフェノールモフェチル",
      "レトロゾール",
      "テネリグリプチンカナグリフロジン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "エルカルチン",
    "correct": "レボカルニチン",
    "choices": [
      "トロキシピド",
      "ジオクチルソジウムスルホサクシネート",
      "レボカルニチン",
      "エストラジオール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ルセフィ",
    "correct": "ルセオグリフロジン",
    "choices": [
      "ソタロール",
      "デキサメタゾン",
      "ベニジピン",
      "ルセオグリフロジン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "コンサータ",
    "correct": "メチルフェニデート",
    "choices": [
      "ビオヂアスターゼ",
      "メチルフェニデート",
      "メコバラミン",
      "バルサルタン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "カナグル",
    "correct": "カナグリフロジン",
    "choices": [
      "バルサルタン",
      "レボブノロール",
      "ロキサチジン",
      "カナグリフロジン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ミネブロ",
    "correct": "エサキセレノン",
    "choices": [
      "エサキセレノン",
      "コハクソリフェナシン",
      "テガフール・ギメラシル・オテラシル",
      "アルファカルシドール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "リフヌア",
    "correct": "ゲーファピキサント",
    "choices": [
      "モキシフロキサシン",
      "ゲーファピキサント",
      "オキサトミド",
      "アロプリノール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "モビコール",
    "correct": "マクロゴールカリウム",
    "choices": [
      "トリアゾラム",
      "マクロゴールカリウム",
      "オメガエチル",
      "フルルビプロフェン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "トビエース",
    "correct": "フェソテロジン",
    "choices": [
      "ラロキシフェン",
      "フェソテロジン",
      "リスペリドン",
      "ホモクロルシクリジン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "リンゼス",
    "correct": "リナクロチド",
    "choices": [
      "セリプロロール",
      "オキシコナゾール",
      "ビオヂアスターゼ",
      "リナクロチド"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "イニシンク",
    "correct": "アログリプチンメトホルミン",
    "choices": [
      "メトホルミン",
      "ブホルミン",
      "アログリプチンメトホルミン",
      "ケトプロフェン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "バクタミニ",
    "correct": "スルファメトキサゾールトリメトプリム",
    "choices": [
      "アラセプリル",
      "バラシクロビル",
      "アジルサルタン",
      "スルファメトキサゾールトリメトプリム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "メラトベル",
    "correct": "メラトニン",
    "choices": [
      "ロサルタン・ヒドロクロロチアジド",
      "バラシクロビル",
      "アルファカルシドール",
      "メラトニン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アテディオ",
    "correct": "バルサルタンシルニジピン",
    "choices": [
      "アゼルニジピン",
      "バルサルタンシルニジピン",
      "シルニジピン",
      "マニジピン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アデホスコーワ",
    "correct": "アデノシン",
    "choices": [
      "テプレノン",
      "アデノシン",
      "フルスルチアミン",
      "ニザチジン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "リパクレオン",
    "correct": "パンクレリパーゼ",
    "choices": [
      "パンクレリパーゼ",
      "アルジオキサ",
      "アクタリット",
      "グリベンクラミド"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ボナロンゼリ",
    "correct": "アレンドロンゼリ",
    "choices": [
      "ベンフォチアミン",
      "アフロクアロン",
      "プレガバリン",
      "アレンドロンゼリ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "エクメット",
    "correct": "ビルダグリプチンメトホルミン",
    "choices": [
      "デキサメタゾンプロピオンエステル",
      "ブホルミン",
      "メトホルミン",
      "ビルダグリプチンメトホルミン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ルパフィン",
    "correct": "ルパタジン",
    "choices": [
      "スクラルファート",
      "オロパタジン",
      "カルシウム",
      "ルパタジン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "バリキサ",
    "correct": "バルガンシクロビル",
    "choices": [
      "バラシクロビル",
      "ファムシクロビル",
      "バルガンシクロビル",
      "アシクロビル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ストミン",
    "correct": "ニコチンアミドパパベリン",
    "choices": [
      "ラミブジン・アバカビル",
      "ドンペリドン",
      "トラニラスト",
      "ニコチンアミドパパベリン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アミティーザ",
    "correct": "ルビプロストン",
    "choices": [
      "ザルトプロフェン",
      "ルビプロストン",
      "アゼルニジピン",
      "イソプロピルウノプロストン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ミニリンメルト",
    "correct": "デスモプレシン",
    "choices": [
      "デスモプレシン",
      "チメピジウム",
      "フラビンアデニンジヌクレオチド",
      "アスパラギンカルシウム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "キャブピリン",
    "correct": "アスピリンボノプラザン",
    "choices": [
      "ベニジピン",
      "トリクロルメチアジド",
      "アスピリンボノプラザン",
      "ペロスピロン"
    ]
  }
]